I've finally waited for this day.
Your Majesty.
You must take good care of the young prince.
All of you, go and prepare.
You actually cured the Gu poison.
How could I lure you in without pretending to be sick?
You really dared to make this move.
Why wouldn't I dare?
This dragon throne,
I was the one who put you on it.
If you can sit on it,
why can't I?
It's a pity
that you can't have your way.
Is that so?
Do it.
Wait.
Grand Princess.
How dare you!
Your Majesty.
I endured all kinds of hardships.
I helped you to the throne.
Are you really going to kill me?
I am your aunt.
I am your only relative left in this world.
Your Majesty.
It's better to just kill her.
I am the Grand Princess.
Let's see who dares to touch me.
I have battled with you for years, Aunt.
Today, you lost by one move.
I
bid you return to your mansion.
Xuan.
I am your own aunt.
You can't.
You can't do this.
How is it?
The Grand Princess was outsmarted by His Majesty
and imprisoned for life.
Useless fool.
Then let's quickly
evacuate the Princess's mansion with our men.
Yes.
Do you think the grapes are sweeter,
or am I sweeter?
How would I know?
Then have a taste.
Brother, I want a taste too.
Ayan, let's not taste it.
By the way, Ayan.
You should go back to your room and rest.
It's getting late.
How about we play with her tomorrow?
But this is my room.
I mean you should rest early.
That way, you'll recover faster, right?
I'm not sleepy yet.
I have a question that I've been curious about.
Why do you always stay by my brother's side?
You've been in the palace for so many years.
You could have continued to move up.
Alright.
I know.
I...
I have a question to ask you.
What is it?
What kind of cooperation should we change to?
What cooperation?
For a lifetime.
User's character goal is 90% complete.
Ayan,
be a good boy.
We really need to rest.
Let's go.
Peel it for me.
Brother.
Can Sister Xiaoyue
sleep here with me tonight?
Ayan, why are you everywhere?
Brother, please go back quickly.
The experiencer's character progress target is 95% complete.
Yuanyuan, what's wrong with you?
I...
Hurry up, let's go!
Brother.
Slow down.
Don't always be in such a rush.
Sister-in-law.
That's not right.
Yuanyuan said before getting married,
the two of you cannot meet.
Otherwise, it's bad luck.
Nonsense.
What bad luck?
We're just...
Report!
Your Majesty, rebels attacked the capital.
They are coming in full force.
What?